snog.com 2013-03-14

# Privacy Policy

Last updated October 31, 2011

## Your privacy is critically important to us. At Snog we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We won't ask you for personal information unless we really need it.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services.

It is Snog's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please send an email to [contact@snog.com](mailto:contact@snog.com).

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Snog collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Snog's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Snog's visitors use Snog. From time to time, Snog may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Snog also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Snog does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Snog choose to interact with Snog in ways that require Snog to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Snog gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website at Snog to provide a birthday and email address. In each case, Snog collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Snog. Snog does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Email Notifications

As a user of Snog you are automatically subscribed to email notifications. Snog sends email notifications when you create an account, a user sends you an answer, a user comments on one of your answers, or a user sends you a private message. Occasionally Snog sends out a newsletter to all of our users to inform them of changes to our website.

## Email Opt-Out

You can unsubscribe directly by clicking the 'unsubscribe' link in any email notification (except the email that confirms your newly created account) or by logging into Snog.com and changing your Account Settings.

You can also request to be unsubscribed by contacting us by email or mail, at:

Unit 201, 1020 Hamilton St  
Vancouver, BC V6B 2R9  
Canada  
Phone: +1 (604) 628-9388  

## Aggregated Statistics

Snog may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to Snog. For instance, Snog may monitor the most popular pages on the Snog site. Snog may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Snog does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Snog discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Snog's behalf or to provide services available at Snog, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Snog, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Snog discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Snog believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Snog, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Snog and have supplied your email address, Snog may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Snog and our products.

Snog takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Snog uses cookies to help Snog identify and track visitors, their usage of Snog, and their website access preferences. Snog visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Snog, with the drawback that certain features of Snog may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If Snog, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Snog goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Snog may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Snog may change Snog's Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Snog's sole discretion. Snog encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Acknowledgment

Snog thanks Automattic for writing a straightforward [Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and making it available under the [Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 2.5 Generic License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/).
